{
    "subject": "resource/Jennifer_Berry",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Houston",
    "human_readable": "Jennifer Berry was born in Houston.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9825422763824463,
            "question": "Is Houston the birthplace of Jennifer Berry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8804650902748108,
            "question": "Where was Jennifer Berry born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7253127098083496,
            "question": "Is Houston a significant location in Jennifer Berry's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6384522914886475,
            "question": "What city is associated with Jennifer Berry's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6060118675231934,
            "question": "What is known about Jennifer Berry's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36618947982788086,
            "question": "What city is linked to Jennifer Berry's birth records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3481498062610626,
            "question": "Can you tell me the place of Jennifer Berry's origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3178521394729614,
            "question": "In which city did Jennifer Berry come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.276252806186676,
            "question": "Where did Jennifer Berry spend her early years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24592150747776031,
            "question": "If you were to map Jennifer Berry's origins, where would you point?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jennifer Berry was born in Houston.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4013_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Jennifer Berry spend her early years?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4013_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which city did Jennifer Berry come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4013_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the place of Jennifer Berry's origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4013_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4013_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4013_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4013_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4013_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4013_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4013_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4013_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4013_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4013_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4013_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Jennifer Berry was born on 18 July 1983 in Houston, Texas, USA,\" which supports the statement that Jennifer Berry was born in Houston."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}